Guide to the New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 Audio Recordings OH.028
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Radio Shows, 1966-1976; 10 audiocassettes; 59 sound tape reels
  - "Report on the Death of a Cab Driver," WNEW-TV, February 13, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0035, Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0233)
    This show covers the death of Ben Cohen
  - Driver Interviews on Death of Ben Cohen, City Hall, February 15, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0035)
  - News Radio (3 Spots), WCBS, June 17, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0234)
  - Harry Van Arsdale on "Searchlight," WNBC-TV, September 13, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0235)
  - "Taxi Industry Story," New York Illustrated, November 3, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0036)
    Arthur Gore, 7:00PM
  - "Man in the News," WCBS TV, November 15, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0037)
    Harry Van Arsdale Interviewed; the tape also includes "assorted unidentified, unedited pieces of recordings" according to its label.
  - Taxi Union News, WINS, November 20, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0236)
  - "Report to the People," WABC, December 6, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0237)
  - "Taxicabs" on WNBC and WCBS, December 20, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0238)
  - "Gypsy Taxi Cabs News," WCBS-TV, January 14, 1971 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0239)
  - "Taxi Cabs," Editorial News, WPIX-TV, January 25, 1971 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0240)
  - Barry Gray Show, WMCA, March 4-5, 1971 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0241, 028_0242)
  - "Newspaper of the Air," WEVD, April 12, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0038)
    11:00 pm. Interviewees: Michael Lazar, George Sandal, Ben Goldberg
  - "Mr. Goldberg: Taxicab Drivers," Barry Farber Show, WOR, May 19, 1971 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0243)
  - "Taxi Cabs," Stan Bernard Show, WINS, September 12, 1971 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0244)
  - Martha Deane Show, WOR, September 23, 1971 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0245)
  - "Midday Live," WNEW TV, December 2, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0039)
    Lee Leonard interviews Michael Lazar, Cal Williams, Harry Van Arsdale
  - "Interview of the Week," WEVD, January 17, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0040)
    Victor Resisel with Michael Lazar and Harry Van Arsadale
  - "Suspects" News Report, February 13, 1976 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0041)
    News report on Rodreguez murder suspects, 13th Precinct
  - WCBS News, February 13, 1976 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0041)
  - "Midday Live," WNEW TV, June 14, 1976 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0042)
    Broadcasted at 12:10pm; Arthur Gore interviewed
  - Barry Gray Show, WMCA, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0246, 028_0247)
  - "Glasgow Death," WHN, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0248)
  - New York Report, WOR, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0249)
- Series III. Educational Programs and Lectures, 1967-1977; 9 audiocassettes; 9 sound tape reels
  Series III. Educational Programs and Lectures (1967-1977) includes class recordings, scholarship award ceremonies, foundation luncheons, and lectures and speeches given by Union members.
  - Governor Rockefeller Addresses New York State Convention -- Transportation Board Issue, Commodore Hotel, October 6, 1967 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0251)
  - Scholarship Program, June 23, 1969 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0250)
  - Traffic and Safety Graduation, April 14, 1970 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0122)
  - Fifth Annual Scholarship Awards, Commodore Hotel, July 7, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0252)
  - Sixth Annual Scholarship Awards, Commodore Hotel, June 15, 1971 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0123)
  - Scholarship Luncheon, Commodore Hotel, June 16, 1972 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0124)
  - Eighth Annual Scholarship Award Breakfast, Commodore Hotel, June 29, 1973 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0125)
  - Lecture by Jim Gilliam, Long Island City, New York, January 31, 1974 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0126)
  - Address by Rosalyn Baxdandall, Labor College, February 23, 1975 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0127)
  - Scholarship Luncheon, Prince George Hotel, June 1, 1976 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0128)
  - Educational Program, July 12, 1977 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0129)
  - Educational Program, July 26, 1977 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0130)
  - Bailin Address on COPE, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0253)
  - Driver Interviews, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0254)
  - George Meany Address, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0255)
  - Scholarship Program Graduation, Undated (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0256)
    Includes speech by Bob Scholl